"@tedcruz And, #HandOverTheServer she wiped clean + 30k deleted emails, explains dereliction of duty/lies re #Benghazi,etc #tcot"
Hillary is our best choice if we truly want to continue being a progressive nation. #Ohio
"@TheView I think our country is ready for a female pres, it can't ever be Hillary"
I just gave an unhealthy amount of my hard-earned money away to the big gov't & untrustworthy IRS. #WhyImNotVotingForHillary
@PortiaABoulger Thank you for adding me to your list
Hillary can not win. Here's hoping the Dems offer a real candidate like Warren. #Warren2016
"Respect FOR the law and respect BY the law Yes, needed desperately.  #BaltimoreRiots"
I don't want to be appointed to an Ambassador post.
"#StopHillary2016 @HillaryClinton if there was a woman with integrity and honesty I would vote for such as woman president, NO"
@HillaryClinton End lawless #ClintonFoundation. Jail Butcher of #Benghazi. #Arrest rapist #BillClinton. #HillaryClinton
"Use your brain, keep Hillary out of the White House.Clinton2016"
@HillaryClinton Hillary pandering with her logo. #ClintonFoundationscandal #ClintonCash
"@readyforHRC @HillaryClinton #HillaryClinton, the US presidency is a testament to the success of #women their role in the world"
@CiaraAntaya cuz you know I'm such a feminist 
2 million bogus followers on Twitter @HillaryClinton #WhyImNotVotingForHillary
@lindasuhler : My name is Rebecca and my grandmother immigrated to Sunnybrook Farm. @twitchyteam
Where's the campaign store is the real question? I am ready to buy some Hillary gear
"It's a miracle, suddenly #Democrats don't mind having someone who voted for war."
@smileitsalicia @greekgummybear2 now i can live in peace
Hillary doesn't want to put anyone in prison anymore. Obviously worried about her own future.
The only way I support Hillary was if Elizabeth Warren ran or Karl Marx was running #2016 #Clinton2016
@HomeOfUncleSam @ScotsFyre @RWNutjob1 @SA_Hartdegen She's too old to understand the internet...that she can be fact checked.
Because Communist Breadlines are not my thing! #NoHillary #WhyImNotVotingForHillary
"@HillaryClinton bad wife, bad role model for women, bad lawyer, bad First Lady, bad Senator, horrible Secretary of State."
"Everything Hillary touches ends up being a scam, a lie, a cover-up, or a failure. William L. Just who we want as president."
Yes HRC subject 2 dbl standard Smh Come on @billclinton @HillaryClinton U Knew @ClintonFdn Donations Would b Scrutinized; Spun!
#Hillary to stop for #pizza today to garner the #Italian vote. #MSM is worthless. #libertynothillary #HillNo
I want America to great again #WhyImNotVotingForHillary
"March 8, 2016 Ohio is holding our Primaries! The date is subject to change. #Ohio #OurChampion"
@RIGHTZONE @WethePeoplePets Let's hope the VOTERS remember! #HillNo
Hillary Clinton has not driven a car since 1996. #clintonfakerealityshow
"@NaughtyBeyotch @TheRealMadman23  Don't care for #Fiorina, but it seems she taking the #sexist gut punches by the #media. #MSM"
"@FoxNews @marthamaccallum @BillHemmer whose the opportunist now, #NoHillary2016"
@HillaryClinton @WomenintheWorld we need to re-establish a #global system dominated by love and affection have #moral_humane RT
#Hillary is as transparent as a brick wall #LibertyNotHillary
@WSJ . Clinton Foundation to keep accepting bribes from foreign governments #WhyImNotVotingForHillary
"@josephbenning I agree, these are better than what you had before, like a severe cold is better than pneumonia. Good luck."
"What are you afraid of @HillaryClinton? If you can't answer questions from the press, why do we want you as POTUS"
"Sorry, Hillary's new normal folk image doesn't take away from Behgnazi & her 0 foreign policy successes as Secretary of State."
CEO pay the target for 2016 election. From someone who makes more than most CEO's but you drank the Kool-Aid.
@NBCNews including repealing the first amendment. Way to go
@NBCNews Stop promoting @HillaryClinton. She is a liar. Just like her impeached husband. #WakeUpAmerica 
Lets take back our country! Whos with me? No more Democrats!2016
"RT @AnthonyCumia: If Hillary IS elected, I have my transition team together to smoothly move me from a racist to a sexist."
I'm #ThatChampion who got kicked off the #Watergate team due to misconduct.  #tcot
.@HillaryClinton is a droid & someone's programmed her to say things - thinks she doesn't have to WORK to win so she ISN'T!
@JVollmer08 @HillaryforIA #freedom_justice_equality_education for innovation and development to make #happy_life i Utopia
Probably not perfect for everyone--which I think is great. But this is the beginning of a conversation.
I'm on the edge of my seat to start volunteering for @HillaryClinton 's presidential campaign!  So excited!!  #cantwait
RT @FutureTXLeader: Is everyone in #ElPaso #Texas ready for president #MarcoRubio #UTEP #NewAmericanCentury #2016 #Future #Rub...
RT @GunnJessica: Because I want young American women to be able to be proud of the 1st woman president #SemST
@Chris_1791 @newsbusters 2 years ago #Hillary never answered whether she used private email #Liberal media passed on reporting #SemST
"@dnewhauser take that, Marco Rubio. @GOP cannot pander to the Latino vote while pushing policies that hurt the community most. #SemST"
@StateDept @AmbCathyRussell @AdamSmith_USA @HillaryClinton @HillaryforIA @BarackObama The whole #world is supporting you. #SemST
Lets remember #dickcheney is an unindicted war criminal b4 we start yelling #Benghazi day after day. Will we ever see justice? #SemST
"Although I certainly have disagreements, after reading about @GovernorOMalley I much rather have him than @HillaryClinton. #SemST"
Human rights are women's rights and women's rights are human rights. - Hillary Clinton #SemST
"Would you wanna be in a long term relationship with some bitch that hides her emails, & lies to your face? Then #Dontvote #SemST"
Bill Clinton just wants to be the first dude to be President and bang one. #SemST
@HuffPostPol If @HillaryClinton can do half of what he did then she would be doing is a favor #SemST
"I've made my decision, to the shock of no one probably, who I'm supporting  #SemST"
"Didn't realize Bob Dole was mentioned in Tupac's ""How do u want it"" #YesterdaysLeaders #SemST"
If I run for office this will be my original logo:          M   #libertynothillary  #HillNo #tcot #UniteBlue #SemST
I will be there when your little tree has run out of smell. #ThatChampion #SemST
crazy to think next up for the Oval Office is either going to be Hillary or a Republican #SemST
@NACLA @BrasilWire SOS OBAMA Who?? @BarackObama ?? :-))))  Are you joking? #StopDilma #StopLula #StopForodeSaoPaulo #SemST
@CheekyGent @ChuckCJohnson Hey Hillary is on her to way to buy votes too! #HillarySoOld #SemST
"RT @NicolaSturgeon: ""It's official: Hillary's running for president,"" says her campaign chief. Excellent! #SemST"
"Only in a SEXIST AS FUK world would we question the ""qualifications"" of a former SECRETARY OF STATE. #SemST"
@ChrisChristie couldn't run his way out of a paper bag let alone beat #HillaryClinton. Go home Chris u r drunk. #ChrisChristie #SemST
"@ReformedBroker ""to da honies gittin money playing #bleep words like dummies"" #POPPA #SemST"
Forgive #CherylRios of her stupid comments about women being president. She will blame it on that time of the month anyways. #SemST
Low key it would be interesting to have a female president. #SemST
"@seanhannity we lost 4,000 of our Military boys when your President pulled out of Iraq.  #LiberalConsequences  #SemST"
.@EthanObama I know - it's just going to be a long year! #SemST
"Technically, a president with raging hormones could refer to estrogen, testosterone or anabolic steroids #IBlamePublicSchools #SemST"
Does Hillary really need to run this country? Could we just make her president of the Bingo club at Shady Pines?  #tcot #p2 #SemST
Lol why do so many people around here hate Hillary?  #SemST
"@HillaryClinton is at the top, and has spent her whole career growing government, keeping the deck stacked. #LibertyNotHillary #SemST"
"Problem with #libertarian is it's not even a decreed party. A house devided against itself, will not stand. think this news to #SemST"
@HillaryClinton i am portuguese and i support your campaign! Best luck! The world need a person and a women like you! #USA #SemST
Hillary Clinton for Ambassador to ISIS. #SemST
"So when all you brave patriots stop Hillary, who you going to replace her with, Jeb Bush? LOL. #losers #SemST"
I'm a woman. Can I be President? @StopHillaryPAC #SemST
This is not her first time at the rodeo!  @HillaryClinton doesn't care who likes her or not This woman is on a mission #Tough #SemST
@lajouetreine @KarrattiPaul I'm not a Genitalian #SemST
Wondering what the NEXT idiotic GOP smear against @HillaryClinton will be. It's coming for sure. Just don't know details yet. #SemST
Hillary is killing it so far on the trail. She's finally showing her personal side and I think it will benefit her profoundly. #SemST
Do we call Bill Mr President...the first 1st man of Or mr president the 1st man? Lol #imreadyforhillary #SemST
.@gailtalk @trscoop Of course it was. She'll be handled every step of the way. They can't risk her unscripted. #SemST
I just want my dog to stop eating the trash #SemST
@thehill @evanperez are you kidding me...leave her to focus on issues...the next prez #SemST
Congratulations @HillaryClinton on entering the 2016 race for President! You have the support of Jews all over the world! #SemST
"@HillaryClinton had more twitter followers then all four major Republican candidates (Bush, Rubio, Paul, Cruz) COMBINED. #SemST"
#HillaryClinton has yet to release @ClintonFdn donors... Public deserves disclosure. #Scandals #lies #Clintons #SemST
I want to go back in time to when men and women couldn't appear in the same yearbook as each other #old school #SemST
RT @hale_razor:#HillaryAccomplishments 1 of select few people fired 4 being 2 unethical 2 investigate Watergate #SemST
How can she live with herself? #Benghazi #SemST
Marriage equality a constitutional right! Woot #HRC2016 #hillaryclinton #readyforhillary #vote #hillaryfor2016 ##mpotus #SemST
Hillary needs to go to a Sheetz gas station after 10 pm to see the real America. #SemST
Hillary's campaign events are scripted dog & pony shows designed to shelter her from vetting b4 the coronation #SemST
"Yes, do tell US, name one of her accomplishments #SemST"
"Apparently, putting cocaine in someone's butthole and then waiting for them to fart in your face is the wrong way to get high. #SemST"
Why is Hillary lying AGAIN about something news worthy? What's news worthy is if she doesn't lie about something #SemST
Chipotle employees shouldn't complain Hillary left nothing in the tip jar. They're lucky she didn't dip in and help herself #SemST
"@Bluesaloon Women are not a demographic, we are at least 50% of the nation. So a woman is no more symbolic than a man #SemST"
Sending u gay bear love from Chicago @HillaryClinton #HillaryMyPresident #SemST
I love the smell of Hillary in the morning. It smells like Republican Victory. #TedCruz2016 #MarcoRubio #SemST
@ProBirdRights: I do a stump speech. It on the stump in the park. attendance mandatory. #SemST
I'd still rather have Aaron Hernandez as President than Hillary.  #SemST
@JSavoly @tedcruz Here ya go teddy boy..the world is getting HOTTER!! It's called GLOBAL WARMING!!  You're such a PUTZ!! #SemST
@JusticeWillett at least he has a platform #SemST
"Because I'm against common core, common crooks and common lies! #NoHillary2016 #StopHillaryClinton2016 #WhyImNotVotingForHillary #SemST"
I would LMAO if some negro Democrat decides to run for President. #HillaryClinton2016 #HillarysBigAnnouncement #HillarysDonors #SemST
"@senna1 @KirillWasHere how many men are getting their dicks sucked daily in congress, etc and no one gives a shit... #SemST"
"You can't grow an economy from the bottom up. If she gets in, we're ALL in trouble #SemST"
@HillaryClinton Stop raising taxes and let people keep more of their wages! #LibertyNotHillary #StandWithRand #SemST
"@theblaze If you think Hillary isn't taking foreign money from Muslim brotherhood, you probably favor Obama as chief justice #SemST"
"3. Fixing America's political system by getting rid of ""unaccountable"" money, and 4. Protecting the country. #SemST"
marijuana? marijuaage equality?? coincidence i think nOT!!11! #SemST
@KoriWasinger @JButtawipo she also voted for the Iraq war and was responsible for gathering @TheDemocrats votes to support it. #SemST
Ding Dong ____ _____ __ ____ #SemST
RT @MaxTollensJr: One-percenter lied about being #DeadBroke No more lies. NO to #SemST
@SLessard 100% agree. We need a woman like Hillary that can help this country get nursed back together! #SemST
Much like you good people I forgot about my #livetweetingbladerunner a couple weeks ago #callback #potroast #cartography #blue #SemST
@RandPaul @HillaryClinton you could never dream to be as intelligent as she is #SemST
"If Hillary will lock Americans in classrooms during her campaign, she'll have no problems locking us all up whenever she wants. #SemST"
"#WhyImNotVotingForHillary she calls education a ""non-family enterprise"" #ImCommitted2DefeatHillary Are you? #ncpol @GOP #SemST"
"@bristola48 @AlciniaH @Mahogany1992 @stphil @MzDivah67 @Progress4Ohio @graceslick77 @AuntLulie @deejayedee He cool, but NO #SemST"
@Jeff_Nichols_82 @HillaryforIA #freedom_justice_equality_education for innovation and development to make #happy_life in Utopia #SemST
@WhiteHouse @BarackObama @HillaryforIA @BarackObama The whole #world is supporting you. #SemST
@HillaryClinton Especially the paid union lackies who have no idea why their there. Propaganda machine spinning overtime. #SemST
@HillaryClinton The deceit hand? Thats a hand you know well. Right? #SemST
@AlyssSmithh There she is pant suite Hillary to hide those thighs #HillarysDonors #HillarysBigAnnouncement #Benghazi #Obama #SemST
@HillaryClinton will pick @SenWarren for VP -Mark my tweet. #UnstoppableTicket #ElizabethWarren #SemST
I'm going to apply for the Intern job #SemST
@TX_1 @politicalmath Then you know how slippery snakes slither over shards of glass! #SemST
@46drhouse - Be interesting to see how Hillary defends same when questioned.  She will eventually have to answer questions. #SemST
.@HillaryClinton What's the ambient temperature in #Hell today? Use that as a guide!  #SemST
"Gov. Chafee, why are you trying to make fetch happen. It's not going to happen. #SemST"
#everydaysexism Only > @ATikSalt < may say what sexism is. The rest of y'all shut up. #SemST
"@tjhansen @owillis serious, if trump runs you'll get a trump tattoo? Calling the Donald!! #SemST"
"Everything abt @HillaryClinton is BOGUS. Her issues, her history, her #Iowa trip, her #Twitter followers, her campaigning #SemST"
#hillaryclinton is a champion of data removal. #SemST
@FoundersGirl @Artist_Angie I want the first female to be competent. #SemST
"Saudi Arabia imprisons & flogs rape victims. ""Women's champion"" @HillaryClinton has accepted MILLIONS $$$ from Saudi govt #tcot #SemST"
How much was Monica getting paid when Bill's burrito squirted sauce all over her pretty blue dress? @MauraReynolds @politico #SemST
Go watch America: Imagine A World Without Her. It'll make you realize how lucky we are to live in the best country on Earth #SemST
I suspect Hillary's Scooby Doo tour is being used as a distraction from ServerGate et al.  #NoObamaThirdTerm #SemST
Breaking News: #Hillary trades campaign bus for a broomstick. #SemST
"@SoCaliMilitia1 @CzarofFreedom  That God for global warming melting icebergs, never gets prosecuted for her crimes #Liberals #SemST"
"Nothing says ""I'm Every Woman"" like 10 Democrat staffers in a machine shop in #Iowa right @HillaryClinton? #NotReadyForHillary #SemST"
"I'd love for some reporter to ask, ""Sec Clinton, will u b returning the White House china, if elected? Or did u already hock it? #SemST"
Very simple: the Clinton's are corrupt. #SemST
.@CaptYonah @thehill Fine; unethical or illegal quid pro quo uranium deal works for me. #SemST
@ConservatveGurl those of us that also have a brain will be voting against Hillary... #SemST
@LifeNewsHQ tolerance at its best! Do as I say not as I do #SemST
"@Chris_1791 @TruthRevolt That doesn't leave much to talk about, then, does it? #SemST"
I'm thinking #Hillary throws #Chelsea under the bus to end #Foundation firestorm.  #ClintonCash #TheGreaterGood #election2016 #SemST
@FoxNews #HappeningNow optics problem? No the real Hillary Clinton has stood up #ClintonCash #IaVotes #SemST
@HillaryClinton You can run but you ca't hide. #ClintonFoundationscandal #ClintonCash #emailgate #SemST
"In case of Emergency, Push THIS BUTTON to scrub server..... #SemST"
Great to see my mentor @RepSusanDavis at #DCinSD. And she's right we have the most qualified candidate ever running for POTUS. #SemST
@BarackObama #Love_peace and peaceful coexistence of all no to violence and #terrorism #SemST
@readyforHRC @HillaryClinton  Support encourage #HillaryClinton president #UnitedStates world is success of women in  world #SemST
I bet Leslie Knope would be so happy about #SemST
"Also the $400,000 ""speaking fees"" #Hillary took from Goldman Sachs for two ""speeches."" @Joan_Vennochi #SemST"
@readyforHRC   Support encourage #HillaryClinton president #UnitedStates world is success of women in  world #SemST
@NatureGuy101 @MaryMorientes   Support encourage #HillaryClinton president #UnitedStates world is success of women in  world #SemST
@rebeccalipson  #freedom_justice_equality_education for innovation and development to make #happy_life i Utopia #SemST
Before leaving my dad's I took the liberty in framing and put up the pictures he has meeting Hillary and Bill Clinton in '92 #SemST
#HillarysAccomplishments Being a total clusterfuck at anything she does. #ReadyForHillary #UniteBlue #TopProg #TPOT #LibCrib #SemST
RT .@ChuckNellis  .@HillaryClinton name change; it's no longer HRC it's now Hillary Uranium #Benghazi Clinton. Take note. #SemST
Hillary is on her way to #Baltimore to be their champion. #BaltimoreRiots #SemST
"take faith that almost every political entity around you, whether dissident or not, serves no good purpose #Dempublicans #SemST"
You don't have to be a lawyer to know the Clintons violated ethics rules. #SemST
@Xxoax @HillaryClinton @MaryMorientes   @BarackObama The whole #world is supporting you. #SemST
@HillaryClinton #freedom_justice_equality_education for innovation and development to make #happy_life i Utopia #SemST
"So @ClintonFdn, I believe Andrew Fastow beat you to the ""we made mistakes, as many organizations of our size do"" excuse #SemST"
I'm 19 years old and care about politics and elections.... I feel like I'm 67 years old #SemST
@HillaryClinton I notice that you didn't condemn the lawless actions of the rioters. #SemST
Obama:  climate change or bush?  Who to blame...?  Hillary:  right wing conspiracy in Baltimore. #BalitmoreRiots #SemST
"Wasn't the original #ScoobyVan also full of unemployed hippies & a stupid dog, who lived to meddle in other people's business? #SemST"
"In 2013 Clinton Foundation collected $140M and spent $9M on direct aid, in 2014 they raised $500M and spent $100M on direct aid!  #SemST"
Students of #BaylorUniversity are y'all ready for #MarcoRubio in #2016 #BU #Baylor #Bears #BaylorBears #NewAmericanCentury #GOP #SemST
@ChelseaClinton @HRC Do you stand for #BillClinton assaulting teen girls too? #ReadyForHillary #HillaryClinton #Clinton2016 #SemST
Hey #TexasState #Bobcats I hope y'all are ready for #MarcoRubio #2016 #TexasStateUniversity #NewAmericanCentury #Texas #TCOT #SemST
"The only thing that I would pay money for is to hear Hillary Clinton say ""I QUIT and I'm GUILTY"" that would be worth millions. #SemST"
"Hillary Clinton keeps sending me emails, and when I try to unsubscribe, I get an error message. THIS IS CANCER #SemST"
@HillaryClinton @BarackObama The whole #world is supporting you. #SemST
"Denial. It works for Hillary, why not the Mayor of #Baltimore. #DemocratLiesMatter #SemST"
Join the Twitter movement! RT or fav for a mention or follow back! #SemST
"Wow RT ""@greta Baltimore Orioles to play tomorrow but no public allowed"" #BaltimoreRiots #FreddieGray #ThanksObama #WakeUpAmerica #SemST"
Spoke to @HillaryClinton today in NYC. Wow! So smart and impressive!!! #SemST
@HillaryClinton Says the millionaire politician who accepts $$$ from countries that execute gays. #Hypocrite #WakeUpAmerica #SemST
"#BernieSanders is running for president, don't the #democrats already have one really old guy running?? #SemST"
297 days until I can register to vote!!1 year 193 days until Election Day #RockTheVote #democrats #everyvotecounts #SemST
"THEYRE NOT ""THUGS""  YOU #TEAPARTY RACISTS THEY ARE ""COMMUNITY REORGANIZERS"" !! #TCOT #baltimoreriots #SemST"
Hillary will get past the primaries cause Dem voters don't think she can do any wrong. But she will be beat in November #SemST
@HillaryClinton loving the new colorful profile pic! #loveit #SemST
"@HillaryClinton Did your rich Saudi donors, who execute gays, join the team? #Hypocrite #WakeUpAmerica  #SemST"
"Also, I finally moved to @FDCITY today! Will be much easier to get around going forward! #moving #SemST"
I think I am going to vote for Monica Lewinsky's Ex- boyfriends Wife #SemST
And the working american tax payer keeps on paying for the unethical liberals who want to destroy this great country of ours. #SemST
Hillary Clinton vs. Bernie Sanders primary will be like the brawl over applesauce at the retirement home. #ReadyForHillary #SemST
Too many women in too many countries speak the same language ¢ÇæÇ” of silence. HILLARY CLINTON #HillaryCliton #Hillary4Women #SemST
Too many women in too many countries speak the same language  of silence. HILLARY CLINTON #HillaryCliton #Hillary4Women #SemST
"Always aim high,work hard, & care deeply about what U believe in...when U stumble, keep faith. HILLARY CLINTON @Faith4Hillary #SemST"
"It's time that we move from good words 2 good works, from sound bites 2 sound solutions HILLARY CLINTON #HillaryClinton #SemST"
@TheDemocrats @DNCWomen I'm down to help for 2016 election. #SemST
How many poor kids could $2.5 billion feed? #SemST
@Norsu2 secret Clinton docs? gee WHAT a surprise! #SemST
Too far @realDonaldTrump. That's just too fucking far. #BaltimoreUprising #Obama #SemST
Hillary Clinton makes Nixon look like an amateur schoolboy #ClintonCash #ClintonFoundation #Clinton #SemST
@thehill #MamaHillary is making the case here & just exclusively how to deal with complex social issues. #cnn #bbc #Mamaclinton #SemST
".@GoldenTalon @johnmanko @CassandraRules  On the contrary, I am happy she will win. I enjoy seeing Liberal cities burn GO #SemST"
Whoever is up now let it be known that support for #MarcoRubio never sleeps! We promote the #NewAmericanCentury 24/7 #Texas #TX #SemST
@Slate This is why Rand Paul will never be POTUS. #BaltimoreUprising #SemST
"@_Poli_Ana_ No, she's got the #BlackLivesMatter vote w/o even talking to them.  Most blacks are brainwashed by @TheDemocrats #SemST"
If you're not watching @HillaryClinton's speech right now you're missing her drop tons of wisdom. #SemST
A proper introduction of Hillary Clinton should begin with five words: Will the defendant please rise #WhyImNotVotingForHillary #SemST
YES! Community policing is answer to rebuilding trust in our communities between law enforcement and the people they serve. #SemST
Don't get it twisted. A major presidential candidate using her first policy speech to talk about mass incarcertaion. #SemST
'Hillary-speak' campaign rhetoric is going to be the death of me. @jmarkwalk #SemST
@HillaryClinton  A Rainbow logo? Did u know only 4% of the US is gay? (2010 Census). #WhyImNotVotingForHillary #SemST
Saw a bit of @HillaryClinton 's speech & I was proud to hear her plans for policy improvements in our justice system. Thanks! #SemST
@Anomaly100 I'm confident that will piss off a few white Anglo-Saxon Protestants!  Keep talking Jeb. #SemST
@Upworthy @HillaryClinton It should be illegal for an employer to discriminate against their workers. #EqualityForAll #SemST
"A body-cam on every cop, private servers for Cabinet Secretaries. #SemST"
@JohnKerry @BALWANIKAPIL @HillaryClinton @StateDept @tomperriello  I didn't realize #PayToPlayDiplomacy was such a big hit!  #SemST
"@VRWCTexan WOW, she's one to talk #SemST"
RT @FutureTXLeader: Are y'all at #UTEP ready for #MarcoRubio in #2016 #Miners #LadyMiners #UniversityOfTexasElPaso #Rubio #New... #SemST
RT @FutureTXLeader: Are y'all #TexasTech #RedRaiders ready for #MarcoRubio in #2016 #TTU #TexasTechUniversity #Rubio #Texas #N... #SemST
RT @FutureTXLeader: Who in #CorpusChristi is ready for #MarcoRubio in #2016 #Hooks #CC #Texas #TX #361 #KeepTexasRed #GOP #Tea... #SemST
"I've been doing my reading and I do have to to say, I'm wildly impressed by Hillary Clinton #SemST"
"@zacharyebell Thank you 4the follow. God bless you and those you love! God bless America, may she always be the land of the free! #SemST"
@BarackObama thanks for selling out all the workers who voted for you for pushing FastTrack #sellout #SemST
As late as 2013 #HillaryClinton opposed marriage equality. #SemST
@thehill all the more reason to vote #Democrat in 2016. #ACAworks #GetMoneyOut #RestoreTheVRA #Bernie2016 #waronpoverty #SemST
RT @Glenn_Hegar: Follow if you stand against Hillary in 2016! #SemST
I can vote in 2016 after all ayyyyyyyyyy #SemST
"@jstines3 @WoodenThreat Open mouth, reveal heart-Margaret Sanger,architect for black genocide @larryelder @TheFive #HillarySoWhite #SemST"
I'm still so happy my voter ID came in the mail  #SemST
Great convo last night w/ @schoolbus_soul & @zaksteib Great connections in #Waverly & on my #turf! #FellowsIA #CommitToCaucus #SemST
#HillaryClinton is hiring #Monsanto lawyers to help her become President. The next president shouldn't be aided by Monsanto #SemST
@marymorientes Love it. It happens in my world too! #SemST
@Froquesha u get me that book yea?  #SemST
RT @putterrod: @IngrahamAngle Republicans everywhere are looking for someone to lead. A leader not a liar. #SemST
This weekend is the Hillary For America Weekend of Action & I hope you'll participate. -L #California #SemST
"It's good that after 30 years in public service (with zero accomplishments), Hillary is finally ready 2 serve the public! Lolol #SemST"
"We're out here in G-town, and where are you  #sctweets #SemST"
@jstines3 @bcwilliams92 #Stephens begged for his life & @HillaryClinton @Madam_President is begging for ur vote #NotAChanceInHell #SemST
RT @spanglishpop: Thanks @GOP keep sending in the clowns! It makes this upcoming election very entertaining #latinos2016 #Rock... #SemST
#ThingsYouDontSayAsAPolitician  I don't feel no ways tired. Go to the back of the line. What difference does it make?  #SemST
Laughing at the Republican Party. The BEST they can offer is #DonaldTrump and #JebBush?   #HillaryClinton has got this! #SemST
"@Temp15544 @icedecay @BrooklynJuggler @classic_mouth In this context, to all practical extents and purposes? It means #SemST"
"Just met an awesome supporter on the CX bus! He said ""Hillary is one strong woman and we need that for our country."" #FellowsNV #SemST"
"Hilary has lied, deleted Benghazi emails, and betrayed the trust of Americans scandal after scandal. #SemST"
"Hillary has lied, deleted Benghazi emails, and betrayed the trust of Americans scandal after scandal. #SemST"
"In high school, decided to be the first woman president in 2016, but I never got into politics & don't have Trump's money. #SemST"
Thanks @izzybugatti for participating! WE are lucky to have YOU here in Iowa. #FellowsIA #SemST
"@jilevin @strumpetcity Yes. You make me proud. Socialism is the answer, which leads to communism. We will succeed. #SemST"
"@GOP Obamacare stays and the Confederate flag goes. You guys have had quite the shitty week, haven't you? #SemST"
Come visit me at the Jefferson County Fair! Representative Curt Hanson will tell a joke and I'll tell a story about why vote #SemST
I'm proud to announce I support #HillaryClinton!!!! #SemST
Excited to be working with some great #FellowsSC this summer. They're some pretty great people that are fired up for #LetsGo #SemST
Federal gov't social spending 61% of budget. Federal gov't defense spending 22% of budget. Something is definitely wrong here. #SemST
@HillaryClinton literally the greatest video I have ever seen. #SemST
@washingtonpost sir sory mae bi bharat mool ka hu par my hart is for democraet and #SemST
@ChelseaClinton's mom has got it going on! #POTUS #ChelseasMom #SemST
"America needs a champion!-H  No thanks,@HillaryClinton we don't need a champion, especially if you're that ""champion"".   #SemST"
Would that the rest of #us were able to escape from #Clinton as well #ClintonCorrectional #HillaryClinton #escapeClinton #SemST
@HillaryClinton Awesome video!  Vote for Chelsea's mom. #SemST
Hilliary: I provided all work related emails  State Dept: There are work related emails you didn't provide  #Hillaredacted #SemST
"#CarlyFiorina on #hannity, very impressive. A serious presidential candidate vs. A bad actress. #SemST"
"@LeighStorz @jstines3 Totally agree, Hillary is an incompetent scandal ridden phony. #SemST"
"This Friday is, officially, Political Incorrectness day! All day say whatever you want and offend everyone! Yay! #tcot #2A #PC  #SemST"
"@FoxNews report shows U.S. State Department cannot locate 15 of Hillary Clinton's Private Emails.  Not so fast, Hillary! #SemST"
@Callisto1947 @texasman2008 @AmyMek Hillary's new Campaign Slogan:  HILLARY - NOTHING TO HIDE EXCEPT THE TRUTH !!!  #TCOT #CCOT #SemST
I really need my new @HillaryClinton shirt to come in. Meeting some people at the brewery same night as a Bernie meetup there. #SemST
"Donald Trump is a joke. His a simpleminded idiot, and I have nothing else to say about him. He can go FUCK him self. #SemST"
@HillaryClinton @ca_hillary stand on the right side #SemST
@HillaryClinton said #AllLivesMatter just like she said marriage was between a man and a woman! Giver her a few more years #SemST
"#HillaryDebateQuestion So you profess admiration for #MargaretSanger who wanted to rid the country of ""negros"". Explain please? #SemST"
RT @mcirelli92: Hillary for the win #SemST
Y did #randpaul take donations from a #WhiteSupremacy group after shaking hands with black leaders? #BlackLivesMatter #gop #SemST
@clairecmc @RosieGray is that why she and @ClintonGlobal take that #Saudi money? #SaudiCables #SaudiCables #clinton2016 #SemST
@petefrt this is how GOP needs to be handling campaign not attacking each other but showing all hillary fails. #uniteright #SemST
@Molls30 @HillaryClinton I love it! One of our biggest donors is Saudi Arabia. They support women's rights completely! #GoTeam #SemST
@HillaryClinton Did you feel same about #BillClinton's latest assault of teen girl? #hypocrite #HillaryClinton #Hillary_2016_NO #SemST
My vote is definitely for Hillary. I don't want Bush's dumb ass. Don't want Trump either.  #HillaryClinton #SemST
"I'm in a better place now that I got some coffee, now time to grow these grassroots   #sctweets #SemST"
"@SCOTUS_Scalia Right. Words no longer have meaning. Like Clintons,""It depends on what the meaning of 'is' is."" More if we don't #SemST"
@tedcruz won't be there. I'm supporting @HillaryClinton for President. #lgbtrights #ACAWorks #SemST
"@GideonHenry First SCOTUS reaffirms Obamacare, then it legalize gay marriage. Your world is crumbling! #SemST"
What a huge win for America! Today is absolutely historic. #EqualityWins #SCOTUSMarriage #SemST
My sexy daddy Obama had two wins this week. Happy for him & democrats   #SemST
@TODAYshow Hillary's emails missing and incomplete? Who'd of thunk it??  JUST TRUST ME!!! #SemST
@vacanti @samglover Maybe a woman should be President.  #SemST
Today LOVE won and Hate was defeated. #MorningJoe #UnitedBlue #SemST
"#Obama is riding high!! #ObamaCare #LoveWins #Republicans tearing out their hair, whatever is left of it ..Next is #SCOTUS #SemST"
Thank you @HillaryClinton for your support of the LGBT community. On this historic day I thank you for giving us hope. #SemST
"A Black President,Healthcare 4 all, Marriage Equality...what's next?..a Woman President?!Damn RIGHT! #SCOTUS #MarriageEquality #SemST"
"RT @muradguderian: Democrats are Red, Obama is a Communist, I'm a true Patriot, So stop Hillary.  #tcot #SemST"
@CBSThisMorning Emails missing and incomplete? Who'd of thunk it?  I'M ABOVE THE LAW and the rest of you peons! JUST TRUST ME! #SemST
Who's monica Lewinsky's favorite football player? Ha-Ha Clinton Dix  #SemST
"SCOTUS dealt a blow to Hillary Clintons last campaign 'promise'... What is she running on now? Corruption, lies, and deceit. #SemST"
"Do America a favor, If you feel you must vote for a woman candidate, Vote for #Carly2016 who at least has integrity unlike #SemST"
Getting another @HillaryClinton bumper sticker because #LoveWins and 2 just wasn't enough #SemST
@pamnsc @TRPhrophet @RamblingMother Thank you for RTs!!! #WakeUpAmerica #dumpboehner #ditchmitch #SemST
"@gerfingerpoken2 he made a careless mistake, she deliberately broke many laws & still lies about it. #SemST"
Very excited to hear Sen. Klobuchar speak today! #SemST
@PolitiBunny @Seja75 @hubbit @HillaryClinton I'm voting in the Democrat primary this year...to support @BernieSanders.  #SemST
My liberty depends on you being free too. President Obama #SemST
@NRO Does @johnpodesta have any grasp on reality? I need more than 140 characters to address someone as naive as this man. #SemST
@JewboyDonny oh I know he won't he effed himself over in the beginning  #SemST
"I called everyone I knew and raised $17,000 from ex-boyfriends - Sen. Klobuchar #SemST"
Great that @HillaryClinton attended #ClementaPinckney 's funeral today!! #SemST
"#WonderWoman movie, #TheMuppets TV show, #StarWarsVII, #MarriageEquaility #Obama. I guess I can leave social media now. Oh wait #SemST"
@politico Remember when millions of GWBush's emails went missing or deleted re Iraq War and nobody had a hearing? Yawn! #SemST
#LoveWins on the day I get my Hillary gear! #Yaaas #Pride #SemST
@thegirlwithfood though. But there are people saying they just aren't going to vote at all which is ridiculous so #SemST
RT @ZerlinaMaxwell: Huge cheer for universal child care and early childhood education. #SemST
Hillary: stop pretending you were supporting the LGBT people when you opposed them until 2013. You are a lying conniving human #SemST
@tedcruz @IamTheWindowMan  GET OUT OF MY STATE YOU BUM! #UniteBlue  #SemST
Whatever is the GOP going to do now with both marriage equality and the ACA? Going to be fun to watch! #SemST
@occupycorruptDC she ain't no ways tired of being a dumbass #SemST
"I AM A CROOK...and I like it, like it, yes I do #HillaryCampaignSlogan  #WakeUpAmerica #StopHillary2016 #specialreport #SemST"
@HillaryClinton Pretty sure you're gonna lose out on a lot of hypocritical #Christian votes by pretending to care about #LGBT #SemST
"Moving forward, our next focus should be making higher education more attainable and eliminating the gender pay gap #SemST"
Let's shatter the glass ceiling! - @GerryConnolly #VAdems #SemST
@JerseyKidPicks thank you sir. It's an honor to hear it. USA for life. Spread this for me. #RememberBenghazi2016 #SemST
"Let's make Secretary Clinton, President Clinton - @AGMarkHerring @vademocrats #SemST"
I think I'll take @JebBush over @BobbyJindal now.. and that is scary to say.  #badchristianvalues #SemST
@kimkennedy4 thats why they still have no voting rights. #SemST
@LaneLewis Thanks for the follow! #TheHRCSuperVols for #SemST
"Sen. Kaine (D-VA) on #SCOTUSMarriage: ""What a great victory! #SemST"
"I am having a really tough time seeing any leaders running for POTUS, quess I will have to wait and see what happens. #SemST"
Hillary flew on private jet to speak to speak about Income & Equality. Dinner plates were $2700.00 ! #EqualityForAll #PJNET #CCOT #SemST
"You're a idiot if you vote for Hillary, her and Obama are The Epitome  of what's wrong with this country #Benghazi #SemST"
"Despite today's ruling, our struggle to end LGBT discrimination is also far from finished - @HillaryClinton #VirginiaJJ #SemST"
"@Jeanelynn Thank you so much for the follow and the FAV, Jeane!!!  Gods' best to you! #WakeUpAmerica #SemST"
My mom just told me she and my aunt want to volunteer on @HillaryClinton's campaign! I support it! #SemST
Let's bring prosperity to the line workers & to the kindergarten teachers!!!- @amyklobuchar #inspiredbyhillary #SemST
"You cant fix stupid, might not be able to vote them out either. #SemST"
If I get killed. Thank @realDonaldTrump . I was tweeting mad crap about him.  I don't take it back. #SemST
Amazing turnout @TheCenterLV . Emotional crowd. RT if agree love wins. #FellowsNV  #SemST
"@megynkelly anytime a liberal throws around words like ""truth is"" or ""reality is"" you know they're about to LIE! #SemST"
@BuffaloBill71 @AramisFraino @pamnsc  Thank you so much for FAVs and RTs!!! #WakeUpAmerica #SemST
@therealjenappel IM HIGH ON HASHTAGS RIGHT NOW I CANT HELP MYSELF #mypresident #SemST
@realDonaldTrump WHY IS IT THAT YOUR CLOTHING LINE IS MADE IN CHINA? Can U say Lier pants on fire? #morningjoe #unitedblue #SemST
SLOWLY SLOWLY THE DEBT CRISIS WILL IMPLODE NATIONS CURRENCY #AmericaDeadBrokeSAVE THE DOLLAR NOW #SemST
#AmericaDeadBrokeSLOWLY SLOWLY China wants the yuan to replace the U.S. dollar as the world's new global currency. #SemST
@HRCSnowShovel it must be hard work burying the @HillaryClinton anti-LGBT rights record #LoveWins #FeelTheBern #SemST
#HillaryClinton We've all been waiting for your rainbow-striped pantsuit  #fashionista #LoveWins #SemST
@JebBush you are set to lose if ur campaign is based on critics instead of proposing #bushfail #SemST
I always joke about anything political bc if I were serious I'd end up offending people and not realize it. #SemST
My dad told me he's voting for Hillary. I'm so proud. LOL #SemST
@dedicated_to_it i think the main problem is having your foot in your mouth in the first place. #SemST
Well Strung is what should happed the next time these Hillary-loving ass douches encounter some trees. #RedEye #SemST
I am just full of myself tonight  #tofunny #funny #funnier #hilarious #HilaryDuff #QuotesOfTheDay #quotestoliveby #quotes #SemST
If I ever meet Hillary Clinton I will have died and then come back to life b/c I will be so happy #idol #SemST
"@ARForHillary @HillaryClinton @HillaryIn2016 So proud of you! Soon, we will show who we really are. Keep up the good work! #SemST"
@HillaryClinton I'd ask #HillaryClinton to stop lying about #Benghazi & #ClintonFoundation ties to #terrorist #muslim #ISIS. #SemST
@HillaryClinton You Flip/Flopped on the Gay marriage issue; must be more votes available with your current view? #SemST
"@HillaryClinton More lies and hypocrisy. As senator of NY, you clearly said you were opposed to gay marriage. #SemST"
@HillaryClinton You have proven your dishonesty once again in flip flopping on this issue. People know you were opposed before. #SemST
@LaureneDiCillo @NBCNews @dl34l And why are major media outlets not exposing Hillary's blatant flip flopping on this issue. #SemST
WHO'S READY FOR A DAY OF ACTION?! I know I am! #FellowsSC #SemST
@DRUDGE_REPORT We haven't even had the elections yet. #SemST
"96 commit cards collected for Hillary in Greenville, SC so far! #FellowsSC #SemST"
"Headed to Chester, SC for a big hillary canvass! Join me. Wylie park 11-3 #SemST"
Save an intern.... Keep Bill & Hillary out of the White House.  #SemST
@HillaryClinton Where are the #LGBT pride condoms #BillClinton used when he assaulted #MonicaLewinsky? #HillaryClinton #tlot #SemST
Fox News predicting 3 way marriage-gee we have the Mormons for that!  #morningjoe #unitedblue #SemST
@philadper2014 @LouiseKatina Hillary's New Campaign slogan is:  HILLARY - NOTHING TO HIDE BUT THE TRUTH!  #tcot #WakeUpAmerica #SemST
Madam President Clinton; you have all the gays vote. #jarrid #SemST
@debaterlife took me a minute to realize where this came from #SemST
@gerfingerpoken @jjauthor one can only hope #SemST
@ReCorwin She didn't even answer with a complete sentence LOL. #Legend #SemST
"Gay marriage is a minor setback for Fox News. Tune in for a full collapse on November 8, 2016. Lots of tears and broken hearts. #SemST"
@HillaryClinton So what's your goal for setting up victims for #BillClinton to assault? #HillaryClinton #ChelseasMom #tlot #SemST
Thanks @Chefs4Hillary for amazing noms for canvassing #FITN #SemST
@LindaSuhler and the sheeple will still vote for her #SemST
"One of Hillary Clinton's biggest idols is Margaret Sanger, who called for the extermination of colored people. #SemST"
@foxnation That should have been done BEFORE she got rid of it!!! #NoHillary2016 #SemST
@GREG61032 @CarmineZozzora @Ash_Bell__  perfect definition of JIBBERISH  #UniteBlue #SemST
"I need @JamesCarville & @HillaryClinton to stop emailing me. I love you, but I need my space. #stillvotingforyou #SemST"
@nytimes this will cost them the 2016 election. #SemST
"HillaryClinton Next up for legalization: Your pet goat, or your #pedophile neighbor 'dating' the 9 year old next door.. #SemST"
@HillaryClinton Will #pervert #BillClinton be there if winner is teen girl? #HillaryClinton #Democrats #liberals #tlot #GOP #SemST
When you fav supports the wrong candidate  (@ladygaga)  #Bernie2016 #SemST
"@koolkat14215 Haha, I LOVE your header! #SemST"
"I hate Hillary Clinton and Obama, please go die together  thrown into the ocean get ripped into prices by sharks. #SemST"
@Raging_D_RTR @CrimsonHotMess I'm for CHANGE and EQUALITY #SemST
.@Theblacksphere #Hillary took a #HypocriticalOath with a vow to do harm to all that cross her. Are you #ReadyForHillary  #GOP2016 #SemST
@lbush34 @HillaryClinton just defending my girl Hillary! #SemST
@larryelder The more Republicans  talk about social policy the better....for #SemST
The only Intelligent Choice for USA is Hillary Clinton....You can not afford to stay HOME ...you must VOTE and VOTE #UniteBlue #SemST
"@fuzislippers @KLSouth @gdebenedetti Yeah, she's a real forward thinker! Lol  #MakeAmericaGreatAgain #WhyImNotVotingForHillary #SemST"
@LibtardLimbaugh @Mex38Tex @NRO Thanks so much for this article! #SemST
I got it! I got it!   A Hillary accomplishment!   She's managed to stay out of prison despite a 30-year crime spree. #tcot #ocra #SemST
@JebBush Here are my thoughts on the ruling: keep your archaic non-science based beliefs out of the laws of our secular nation #SemST
"@Reince Facts confirm what we knew. Used server to prevent e-mails from becoming public records. Like Obama, no transparency. #SemST"
Republican candidates continuing to spread hatred and alienating the voters. Hillary wins!  #LoveWins #MikeHuckabee #Rubio2016 #SemST
Hillary Clinton might end up having my vote. She's been tackling so many issues that America needs to face. #SemST
Apple and Walmart = MADE IN CHINA Why does our country continue to sell us out to China in every way possible? #AppleMusic  #SemST
if Hillary wins the election there's a chance we might move to Australia. #HILLARY4PRES #SemST
@ghostseven77 WE HAVE A TROLL ! #morningjoe #unitedblue #SemST
"Dick Morris: @HillaryClinton is ""fundamentally corrupt"". He should know! #copolitics  #wcs15 #SemST"
@WestonMartinez @crazytas62 Cruz needs to autograph bomb #SemST
"@CidEloisa @DiggingLamb Thank you so much for RTs and FAVs, Eloisa and Thomas!!! #WakeUpAmerica #SemST"
My how times have changed: @MartinOMalley has focused his attacks on @BernieSanders not @HillaryClinton #SemST
@moser_kristen  I love how you pay more attention to the democratic candidate than you own republican candidates #KnowTheEnemy #SemST
& I bet that @HillaryClinton is thee best choice for President in 2016she's the next best one for the people  #Vote #SemST
Can't wait to get my #YaaasHillary shirt!  @HillaryClinton #SemST
@realDonaldTrump @WhoopiGoldberg @Univision #VoteForHillary @HillaryClinton isn't racist. A leader who demands #EqualityForAll #SemST
@dhz26 I love a good sale. Money well spent. 2 birds with 1stone. #LoveWins #SemST
H stands for Holding Back e-mails belonging to #WeThePeople #obstructingjustice #WakeUpAmerica #HillaryLiesMatter #UniteBIue #SemST
"Bernie or Hillary? Prefer Bernie but Hillary fine. Either way, Dems gotta stand together in 2016. #FeeltheBern #SemST"
"#HillaryClinton might want to book smaller venues for her rallies, if not many empty seats will be seen on TV, that's bad lol #SemST"
@WNTonight i love bernie because he ain't #SemST
"Night, sleep tight, don't let Hillary bite. says @Tony_Tickets   ""Nightmares"" is all I say.  #SemST"
@foxandfriends How could we support it if it was secret??? #NoHillary2016 #SemST
"Why is HRC so popular?  This deceptive socialist accomplished nothing. Is only wife of an impeached President, who enabled UBL.   #SemST"
2016 is going to be a great year. Rush Limbaugh's contract is over and he will be dropped by so many. Liberal victory #stoprush #SemST
@HillaryClinton R U desperate or what? 3rd Hillary tweet on my timeline 2day. NOT gonna vote 4 U! #SemST
@awj9009 not at all I think the statute of limitations has expired plus I can always have a driver ala #SemST
"Never vote for @RickSantorum ""for the survival of our country"" #LoveWins #SemST"
@voxdotcom   #wgn #WGNTV - now mentions ROMNEY? #Hillary CARE = ROMNEY CARE = #Obamacare -- now PUBLIC OPTION for ALL #SemST
@BDabs888 let's go shoot your now today. #SemST
"I guarantee Hillary could care less about black rights.  If Obama did, blacks wouldn't be in the same predicament still.  #SemST"
"Hillary LIES, yet people still desire her as the President of the United States. #sad #SemST"
@17leete17 hahaha. He is some kind of special..  this is why Hillary's going to win! Hahaha. #SemST
@realDonaldTrump @MalachiNorris lol!!!!  That is one of the funniest things I've heard in a while!!!!  #SemST
Remember back when #CrackerBarrel gave in 2 #PoliticalCorrectness over #DuckDynasty ? #Wakeup #NASCAR  b4 it's to late  #tcot #SemST
Will the media ever get real with Hillary? #2016 #Benghazi #Clinton #SemST
"Last week = Life (Obamacare, gay marriage)  Today = Death (air pollution, lethal injection)  Elections matter, y'all. #SCOTUS #SemST"
Do you know what would REALLY PISS .@HillaryClinton OFF?  .@VP .@JoeBiden runs against her. LMAO!   #WakeUpAmerica No longer is #SemST
Is there a Govt restart button? Someone needs to push that thing. #RememberBenghazi2016 #PatriotsWillRise #SemST
"Bad punning gets worse, not better, over time. Remember that, America #SemST"
"#Putin, the last thing the US needs right now is another #Clinton or #Bush in the White house. We're a dynasty now? #Jeb2016 #SemST"
Hillary's New Campaign slogan is:  HILLARY - NOTHING TO HIDE BUT THE TRUTH!  #tcot #WakeUpAmerica #SemST
@GOP Of course @HillaryClinton is silent. That insures she doesn't have 2 stand 4 ANYTHING & less chance of offending voters #SemST
Don't you someday want to see a well qualified candidate by the president of the United States? #ReflectingHillary #SemST
"It's Monday night,do you know where your Hillary supporters are? In Rock Hill at our Amazing Phone bank! Come join!HillaryforSC #SemST"
Casually hangin' with @HillaryClinton on a conference call while taking a break at #ACUHOI. #SemST
Our Queen City is currently infested w/ out-of-state plate Priuses driven by millennials w/ Hillary bumper stickers. #MHT #SemST
Gwen being a good leader and training a new volunteer in rock hill.! #FellowsSC #HillaryForSC #SemST
"#DemocRAT2014Slogans: ""Why work? When you can VOTE DemocRAT - twice!"" #tcot #SemST"
@HillaryClinton Yes I can and will. #SemST
@HillaryClinton Yes! I am chipping in 5$ because we have faith in you. #SemST
@AndreaTantaros @3coffeesplez WTF? This just keeps getting crazier! #SemST
"Apparently, @BernieSanders fans don't like to see Hillary's name even implied.  #SheWhoShallNotBeNamedBecauseShesWinning #SemST"
Fantastic Emmet County Dem meeting tonight in Estherville. Glad to meet some @HillaryClinton supporters! #SemST
"Gay Rights are Human Rights, and Human Rights are #GayRights - @HillaryClinton #HillaryForAmerica #SemST"
I think it's funny people think Bernie can take on Hillary and Bill #SemST
As much as @BernieSanders's poll numbers have jumped I still have Hillary winning the Dem. nomination. #SemST
@PhilGlutting @megadreamin Thank you so much for RT and FAV!!! #WakeUpAmerica #Rubio2016 #Cruz2016 #SemST
@marcorubio will not let our enemies take advantage of us like Obama is doing & Hillary will do! @TeamMarco #NewAmericanCentury #SemST
Just think how many emails Hillary Clinton can delete with today's #leapsecond #SemST
The kind of Gov that Liberals promise you can only be achieved and sustained with a Conservative Government.   #HeatWave #tcot #SemST
@TIMENOUT Is there anything about the Clintons that is not fraudulent? #SemST
@HillaryClinton > since trickle down economics has failed when was the last time a poor person created jobs? #SemST
@petefrt That woman is so corrupt she can't even have a truthful thought. #SemST
It's official. Every single #GOP member is now a candidate for #POTUS. Who needs #leadership when you have a #soapbox? #SemST
"So glad @ChrisChristie has announced his candidacy - fits right in with all the other ""qualifies"" republicans on the list. #SemST"
"Hillary claims to be a ""champion"" of the middle class, but @RandPaul tax plan cuts the FICA tax, benefiting the middle class. #SemST"
It is offensive when the mexican flag flies on US soil. California state capital. #Lovewins #univision #foxnews #DonaldTrump #SemST
Can anyone name the jobs #HillaryClinton has been responsible for creating.. Even her security is an entitlement... #SemST
"@LeahR77 @DrMartyFox > With continued #Obama's & @TheDemocrats Admin policymaking, #USA will become #Greece! #WakeUpAmerica #NJ #SemST"
@johnpodesta @HillaryClinton awesome every true chef needs this.. Go Hillary #SemST
@CorrectRecord is quite obsessed with emails and transparency. Why did Hillary Clinton destroy her emails? #clintonemail #SemST
@Logan_RTW I agree with her previous stance; and I'm sure she still believes in what was said before. #SemST
@HillaryClinton Hahahaha how much are you going to charge them!!!! #NoHillary2016 #SemST
#AskBobby Do you think #HillaryClinton has turned over all of those emails on her private server she destroyed! #SemST
@FoxNews we just have to hang in there long enough that this idiot doesn't completely destroy the country #SemST
#AskBobby would you blame an obscure film maker for the death of #USAmbassador in #Benghazi like #SemST
I feel confident that @HillaryClinton will win  in 2016. #SemST
"@asphaultangel13 Afterall, they're just a poor black family trying to pay the bills!  @crousselle #WhyImNotVotingForHillary #TCOT #SemST"
Great day in Emmetsburg meeting with #HillaryClinton supporters and learning more about important issues in Palo Alto county #SemST
"Is a Eric Holder making 7 figures in the financial industry he protected from prosecution, yet?  Why do Libs love 1%ers?  #SemST"
Fashion News: Hillary has a new clothing line coming out called Flip Flops R US   #tcot #Benghazi #SemST
@Jami_USA I'm just hoping we don't have to resurrect the no H8 for Hillary's second term. #SemST
U Missouri at KC got Chelsea caus Hils cost too much. Chels could arrive w/ mom - no xtra charge. @HillaryClinton #SemST
@GovChristie can't even run NJ and wants to be president? I'd vote for him before @HillaryClinton #SemST
"RT @HillaryHaikus: #Ready because one day girls will say: I want to be President, too.  #ReadyForHillary #haiku #SemST"
@PhxKen Shocked she didn't burst into flames! #WakeUpAmerica #makeAmericaGreatAgain #SemST
so @AdamParkhomenko met @oliviawilde . there aren't enough words to describe my envy haha #SemST
@robin45208 @C4Constitution Thank you so much for RTs!!! #WakeUpAmerica  #SemST
Republican donors have numerous candidates to put their money on. Dems basically have one. We're gonna get killed financially. #SemST
Can @DavidCornDC help Cuckold Conservatives win in 2016!  More cuckoldry please!  #Christie2016 #DonaldTrump #UniteBlue #p2 #SemST
Chris Christie for President? HAHAHAHAHA!  I don't think so!  @HillaryClinton #Clinton #Hilary #SemST
@megynkelly Hahahaha combed through emails!!! Bunch of scumbags!!! #NoHillary2016 #SemST
Loved talking with Yvette today about education and women's voices in politics. Can't wait to see her on caucus day! #FellowsIA #SemST
"#BENGHAZI WAIT DID I SAY ""THANK GOD?"" VOTERS? SRY!! MT!! I MEANT ""THANK GOODNESS!"" NO OFFENSE INTENDED! ##tcot #SemST"
@pikester45 Exactly what I don't want to see happen in America. #SemST
"@Lawrence @TheLastWord There is no enthusiasm gap, Mr. Lawrence!    -@TheHRCSuperVols   @JW4Hillary @kimfrederi #Hillarymen #SemST"
@HlLLARY @ToniforAsm Hillary for Prez = Obama's third term and that's the last thing we need!! #SemST
@businessinsider One thing that's painful is the mindless minutiae her strap hanging cling-ons force her to endure. #huma #SemST
The guy in the multicolored shirt looks chi as fuck. #SemST
Insurgent. What will happen if Hillary becomes dictator in chief. #SemST
How can we expect u to make good financial decisions for the US if u can't manage ur own multimillion $ salary so ur not broke #SemST
"@liars_never_win @HillaryClinton shhh, go get me an iced tea..... #SemST"
@FoxNews @GovChristie @HillaryClinton Actually she should be disqualified from running!How many scams and ethics problems now? #SemST
#Christie2016 you can't claim #Bridgegate wasn't your fault when you were the man behind the wheel. #GOP  #TeaParty #TCOT #DEM #SemST
@Debber66 @andersonDrLJA She will be a  #CenterHitler. #SemST
"@HillaryforNV @MissLynnetteH 2 hours left, let's chip in $5, Nevada! #raisethenewPOTUS #SemST"
How anyone can believe a single word that comes out of that woman's mouth is beyond me... #SemST
RT @Waitingforahero: 2nd tweet-#POTUS2016 candidates #guncontrol Read article-esp #JebBush (make #GunViolence worse) & #GunSen... #SemST
@HillaryIn2016 hey I just checked your blog. Kudos! Keep it up! #SemST
"The owner of Univisin, donated as much as $25 million to the Clinton Foundation, his wife sits on its board #Univision #Trump #SemST"
Hillary had just enough time to doctor her email inbox to her advantage before releasing them.... hahaha #justkidding #SemST
".@davelevinthal Operating a shredder, now @hillaryclinton is WAY more adept at using THAT! #WakeUpAmerica #TCOT #OhHillNO! #SemST"
"@theblaze gee,  what a busy schedule she had. #SemST"
So you're used to the @AP calling for your approval before running a story @davidaxelrod?   #LikeHillary #HillaryEmails #SemST
"White, middle-aged men did a pretty good job leading this Country for 230 yrs. Racist? Sexist? No, I'm a realist. #SemST"
It's more than mistakes...with #HillaryClinton lying and cover-ups are a way of life. @NormanSie @n2toom  #tcot #uniteblue #SemST
Hillary can't use a fucking fax machine but you idiots are going to vote for her to be President?  #SemST
@gerfingerpoken2 #hillary is most likely a felon many times over but has been protected by the political class. #SemST
@HillaryClinton you have my support. (Now lets see how many people unfollow me.) #2016election #SemST
#Hillary's still very weak among grassroots - as shown by how strong #BernieSanders got how fast on how little. @AaronBlakeWP #SemST
"Now that #Hillary is raising money like an incumbent president, can we stop pretending that she won't be the nominee? #SemST"
"All Americans have value to our society, it's called a vote. #LiberalLogic    #InternationalJokeDay #SemST"
Free market capitalism is America's best friend because of constant pressure to innovate & use resources efficiently. #SemST
Thank you for your kind RTs and FAVs @pamnsc !!! #WakeUpAmerica #todosmarchamos #Cuba #SemST
Hillary's campaign raised $45 million  91% of all donations were $100 or less  This is a record. Beating Obama's record in '11 #SemST
Win with the Blacks. Put some of your focus on the racial tension between Blacks and Whites. #SemST
".@NewtGingrich on @HillaryClinton: ""She's very formidable... she's a very competent person. #SemST"
@WashTimes @BretBaier Why is there no outrage about all the smoke & mirrors w/ this candidate? Are you hiding Hill! #SpillHill #SemST
I'm really excited for 2016 after finding out the amount @HillaryClinton raised. We got this. #SemST
@docdebags @awelab1956 @BuzzFeedAndrew @BuzzFeedNews  It will. Otherwise we're guaranteed GOP in control of all 3 branches. #SemST
.@DavidLimbaugh - agree put it back.. But I have a feeling it won't go away.. It will keep coming back! #SemST
"of lear jets and fax machines...LOL @HillaryClinton ""woman of the people"" HA! #BestTheyveGot #SlushFund #UraniumDeal #SniperFire #SemST"
.@FoxNews @brithume ok.. So where are these emails coming from? Didnt @HillaryClinton already say the server was erased? #LIES #SemST
I dreamt about Hilary Clinton last night. Does this mean her plans to control us and take over the world are coming true? #SemST
@CoachDLG515 @Retired36 I'm glad that you will now slice all round.  #SemST
#Obama administration lies again.. Knew of #HillaryEmails being private.. transparency???? #SemST
"Dude, why can't Hillary run a fax machine?   #SemST"
@jimlibertarian @peddoc63 @Callisto1947 @MaydnUSA @c5hardtop1999 @surfermom77 @SMolloyDVM That's right! #SemST
If a man demanded staff to get him an ice tea he'd be called a sexists elitist pig.. Oink oink #Hillary #SemST
@HillaryClinton will be the nominee for the Democratic Party. Period. And she's gonna win the Presidency too. #SorryBernie #SemST
"@RNRNewYork in her #Emails @HillaryClinton said there were ""a couple of Facebooks"" on her :) #TotalIncompetence #RedNationRising #SemST"
"@DrMartyFox @BossHoggUSMC @JohnFromCranber @seanhannity @SheriffClarke Fine, they can leave USA & never come back. #OiP #Cruz2016 #SemST"
"My birthday is on July 24th, if anyone needs a gift idea #ChillaryClinton #SemST"
LOOKING FORWARD TO #CUBA EXPANDING MAJOR EXPORTS OF PICK UP TRUCKS CONVERTED INTO RAFTS!! SO EXCITING! #tcot #SemST
@POTUS I want you to President for a 3rd term!!! Please make it happen LOL! I'm fine with #SemST
#AskPOTUS Would you fire the #GOP congress for not doing their job if you could? #GOPFail #SemST
@jhewitt1280 @SpeakerBoehner @HouseBenghazi @TGowdySC What her emails? They released the rest all very boring. #SemST
"hey ""transparent"" @HillaryClinton so...who is ""Santa""? #LibHack #Pay2Play #Corruptocrat #tcot #Benghazi #VinceFoster #Monica #SemST"
"Take it easy Ed, #BernieSanders is a side show. Democrats are having some fun before getting back to reality in Nov 2016.  #SemST"
The Kool-Aid drinking leftanistas continue to close ranks with support for Madame Secretary. WTF? Hillary is a fraud full of lies. #SemST
"Trump's inauguration speech (God Forbid)!!.....Me-me-me-me-China-me-me,""did i mention me yet!?..where's my hairspray China #SemST"
#KCA #VoteJKT48ID RfWheels3015: davidjones720 rratkinson Right I mean what the heck is an #ArabDonorGroup ?? #HillaryEmails #D... #SemST
@HillaryClinton is opening 10 more offices in Iowa this week.  She's not playing around! #iacaucus #SemST
Obama give Americans OVERTIME Pay! Republicans give Americans Welfare Checks! #tcot #UniteBlue #SemST
"Make sure to make it to the Brew House in Pella, IA tomorrow @ 3 to meet with @HillaryClinton supporters! #SemST"
#Univision ignores Latino candidate Marco Rubio because he doesn't fit their narrative.They're invested with Hillary #rubio2016 #SemST
"Overheard at the Davenport open house: ""Oh, I know you from Facebook!"" #DigitalOrganizing #SemST"
"@TODAYshow @ChrisChristie is not qualified b/c he eats $82,000 in snacks & b/c of D corruption of #Bridgegate  A BIG FAT BULLY! #SemST"
@AutumnNAlston @JonathanDKF @_sarah_babb_ @McCollumMike @HillaryClinton @HillaryforSC Inaugural tweet from our new account! Go #SemST
"@hughhewitt like I tweeted you way back when, #ACA software can be fixed , but GOP strategic mistake of 'repeal' can't be fixed #SemST"
@msnbc @Lawrence @JoeBiden @SenSanders  we love Joe and Bernie--but they ARE too OLD--they would end up a #OneTerm President #SemST
HER NAME IS RIO AND SHE DANCES IN THE SANAAAAAND!!! WHOOOO!! #tcOT #SemST
@RobBently @JonahNRO @BernieSanders Hillary campaign  will shortly announce that Sanders was born in Canada. Yeah that's it. #SemST
"Bill Clinton Decided against taking out Bin Laden.   And we Got September 11, 2001.  #SemST"
@politico   YAWNzzzzzzzzzzzzzz could keep the z's going for the full amt of Tweet characters but you get the point. #SemST
"The Democrats are not creating Al QAEDA, they are creating A NUCLEAR ISIS.  THINK ABOUT THAT.  #SemST"
Kind of scares me that there are still thousands of emails that have not been released from Hillary's private emails.  #SemST
"#TheDonald can't keep a beauty pageant afloat and wants to be the President?  Aw, hell no. #SemST"
You know emailgate must be going nowhere when Fox News are hashing out the Bosnia 'sniper fire' story again. #SemST
BIG BOOTY BITCHES BIG BIG BOOTY BITCHES #SemST
"@maddow I love Bern, but it's not his time! #SemST"
It's what's best for business and presidential seat for #HillaryClinton  #SemST
It's great that @JebBush supports GMO crops. It's like the IT scepticism all over again. Science vs belief. #JebBush #SemST
"Folks, this is what happens when Liberals are in control! All hell breaks loose! Had enough yet? #SemST"
If you need me I'll be screaming like a little baby from now until about ten minutes after @HillaryClinton arrives in #PTown. #SemST
The biggest dumps of bad info is b4 a holiday weekend. What comes out of WH and state dept today? #HillaryEmails  #LiarLiar #SemST
Leader of free world. Global navigating. Interacting with the international community. Beyond big crowds. Learned lesson. #SemST
Those aren't pantsuits. They are camouflage outfits carefully tailored to minimize silhouette. Think stealthsuits.Very high tech. #SemST
Just ordered my Chillary Clinton Koozies. Gotta support the team. #SemST
We can't expect change if we continue to vote for the same people. You have to take a chance 4yrs is not that long #Bernie2016 #SemST
@realDonaldTrump not good when only @AnnCoulter defends you. Your big mouth & giant ego are your downfall #stupidisasstupiddoes #SemST
"Hillary must have been at the Navy Yard, under sniper fire!  #SemST"
"@JW4Hillary @MrDane1982 I choose ""it takes a village! #SemST"
"@mizerello @meetthepress at least he didn't lose an embassy, cover up a murder, or burn govt emails. #SemST"
#HILLARY has been lying for so long that her first fib was in morse code #HillNo2016 #SemST
EVERYDAY AMERICANS AND THEIR FAMILIES NEED A CHAMPION AND HILLARY WILL BE THAT CHAMPION.   #SemST
#INeedMeninist because @HillaryClinton is running for president...do I need to say more? #SemST
Cruz-- Perry 2016 @tedcruz @GovernorPerry It's the only win-win choice #SemST
#CPC thinks they can run antisocial personal attack advertising on #socialmedia! LOL! #cdnpoli #StopHarper #FeelTheBern #fnpoli #SemST
@CBSThisMorning Bernie Sanders had record crowds in Madison wis why no mention from you guys you talked about trump #Trump #SemST
Was asked by @HillaryClinton to help with her campaign. Gladly (excitedly) accepted! #SemST
"@HillaryforIA come on, Iowa! For better USA and the ROW #SemST"
"Pundits say Jim Webb facing uphill battle with Hillary.  Really, it's with Bernie for the anti-Hillary vote.  #JimWebb #SemST"
Exciting to hear more about our Fellows all across the country on tonight's call. Special shout-out to the #FellowsIA. #SemST
@AnitaFinlay @politico Hillary's doing the right thing -- staying focus on her campaign. #SemST
@chicagotribune #ayyylmao do #Democrats & other #liberals realize no one wants #HillaryClinton which is #Obamanation 2.0? #SemST
"@betheljd Thanks for the follow David, may God bless you and your family.  #freeallfour #SemST"
"@Network_Citizen @ProudInfidel33 @YoungBLKRepub ""@HillaryClinton can't even manage @billclinton and she wants to be @POTUS"" #lol #SemST"
"@sunbeltgirl @9975Ts @bobwilsonn ""@HillaryClinton can't even manage @billclinton and she wants to be @POTUS"" #lol #StopHillary2016 #SemST"
"@WoodenThreat @ProudInfidel33 ""@HillaryClinton can't even manage @billclinton and she wants to be @POTUS"" #lol #SemST"
"@kin2souls @sunbeltgirl @ChristiChat ""@HillaryClinton can't even manage @billclinton and she wants to be @POTUS"" #lol #SemST"
"@RedStateJake ""@HillaryClinton can't even manage @billclinton and she wants to be @POTUS"" #lol #WakeUpAmerica #StopHillary2016 #SemST"
@gerfingerpoken Why is this woman like teflon?  She has committed enuf egregious crimes she should B superglued 2the dang wall! #SemST
"@Babbsgirl2 ""@HillaryClinton can't even manage @billclinton and she wants to be @POTUS"" #lol #WakeUpAmerica #StopHillary2016 #SemST"
"@ResistTyranny ""@HillaryClinton can't even manage @billclinton and she wants to be @POTUS"" #lol #WakeUpAmerica #StopHillary2016 #SemST"
"@weknowwhatsbest ""@HillaryClinton can't even manage @billclinton and she wants to be @POTUS"" #lol #WakeUpAmerica #StopHillary2016 #SemST"
@randyprine @fabiaceae They know they're going to lose to HRC so they keep trying! #SemST
"@realDonaldTrump ""@HillaryClinton can't even manage @billclinton and she wants to be @POTUS"" #lol #WakeUpAmerica #StopHillary2016 #SemST"
If you support @HillaryClinton you are supporting another term of the policies of George W Bush. #democrats #mepolitics #SemST
@Shy_Buffy welcome little sister! Love you! #SemST
"@politico @anniekarni ""@HillaryClinton can't even manage @billclinton & she wants to be @POTUS"" #WakeUpAmerica #StopHillary2016 #SemST"
"@oreillyfactor ""@HillaryClinton can't even manage @billclinton and she wants to be @POTUS"" #lol #WakeUpAmerica #StopHillary2016 #SemST"
"@FoxNews  ""@HillaryClinton can't even manage @billclinton and she wants to be @POTUS"" #lol #WakeUpAmerica #StopHillary2016 #SemST"
"@politico  ""@HillaryClinton can't even manage @billclinton and she wants to be @POTUS"" #lol #WakeUpAmerica #StopHillary2016 #SemST"
Another #Hillary supporter committed to caucus tonight! One more step on the way to winning the Iowa caucus. #SemST
"@TIMENOUT  ""@HillaryClinton can't even manage @billclinton and she wants to be @POTUS"" #lol #WakeUpAmerica #StopHillary2016 #SemST"
So thankful for all of the volunteers who joined us at Bliss Studio in Fairfield tonight! #Rockstars #SemST
The most revealing part about Hillary's released emails is that they're pretty much as boring as mine. #nofriends #SemST
"@FrankCraig: @skzdalimit if you're the best your side has to offer, we have nothing to worry about, slick. #SemST"
"@RAM0018 @joanwalsh @Salon @BreeNewsome @chrislhayes Without the blacks and minority voters? NO, Won't happen! #SemST"
@popcornreel @joanwalsh @SenSanders @BernieSanders He is what he is and it doesn't resonate with minority and black voters! #SemST
@awadgolf @Crossbearer1956 @ScottSaxman1 This is why I'm not voting for Hillary #SemST
@foxnewspolitics NOT EVEN A LITTLE BIT!!! #Nobama #WeMissYouGipper #SemST
"#Putin, #NothingMoreAmericanThan voting based for a politician to lead the country when she can't even handle email. #think #SemST"
"#Putin, #NothingMoreAmericanThan voting for a politician to lead the country when she can't even handle email. #think #SemST"
2 people that are surprising? Trump &Fiorina. Why? Cause they're being honest w/what they think.  Obama built that.  #SemST